hoopgame.net 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy of HoopGame.net

This privacy policy covers how we treat personal information that we collect and receive. We do not intend to collect any personal information from children under 13 unless we believe such collection to be permitted by law. Please see below for our policy with respect to children under 13. 

**General**

We gather user information to provide you with a customized experience on our site. Your user information helps us tailor the content, services, goods and advertising to your current and future needs. For this reason, we may ask you to register when you visit certain areas of our site. If you choose not to register you may not have access to areas that require personal identification. 

**Use of Information**

When you register, we only ask for a unique nickname and password selected by you, and your password is encrypted in our database. 

All communication on the Internet takes place between pairs of IP Addresses. Our Web servers will log the IP address that any connection is made from. We may use these IP addresses to help diagnose technical problems or prevent abuse of our systems or other site users. Your IP address may also be used to gather aggregate demographic data and target advertisements accordingly. 

Your browser has options to accept, reject, or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored with your Web browser for record-keeping purposes and to help us provide better service to you. We use cookies to save your password (in an encrypted format) on your machine so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. 

We use companies to serve the advertisements on some of our pages. These companies and advertisers may place and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours. We may use your information or allow advertisers or companies that serve advertisements access to your information to determine which advertisements you will see. This information may include your demographic information, geographic location, what content you access on our site, how you rate various content and other information. 

Our site contains links, including banner and other ads, to other Websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Our site may also link to Websites that feature our trademarks and names along with trademarks and names of other companies. You should look at the privacy policy on that co-branded Website, as the co-branded Website may not be under our control. 

For reasons such as improving member experience and providing customized communications to our users, we may receive information about you from third party sources and our web logs and add it to the information that we have received from you. Web logs automatically record anything a web server sees, which may include e-mail addresses you enter into a form or pages viewed by a user at a particular IP address. 

**Information Sharing**

We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties, aside from entities that perform services for us. 

However, we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety. 

In the event that we acquired by another company, your personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party. 

**Google Analytics**

HoopGame make use of Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. HoopGame may also make use of other Google Analytics for Display Advertising features, including Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting and/or the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration. We are required by Google to disclose the following information to you in our Privacy Statement in connection with our use of any Google Analytics for Display Advertising features on HoopGame.Com: 

You may opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising or customize Google Display Network ads by using the [Google Ads Settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). You may also prevent your data from being collected and used by Google Analytics by opting out through the use of the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

If HoopGame make use of the Google Analytics for Display Advertising Remarketing feature, HoopGame will use such Remarketing feature to advertise online and third party vendors, including Google, may show HoopGame ads on sites across the Internet.

HoopGame and third party vendors, including Google, may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on a user's past visits to HoopGame, and/or (b) report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to HoopGame.Com. 

Data from Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting may be utilized by HoopGame to help recognize and understand user preferences, to make improvements to HoopGame.Com, to choose content and advertising to display to you, and for other business purposes that will allow HoopGame to better serve you.

**DoubleClick DART and Third-Party Vendors Cookies**

We also may use DART and third-party vendors cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART cookies use "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>  
Third parties, like Google, may collect certain types of information about visits to the site, including interaction with content on these sites. As always, no personally identifiable information will be collected. 

**Children Under 13**

Our site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We respect the privacy of parents and children and are committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). On those areas of the sites that ask for age, we do not collect personal information from individuals who identify themselves as under the age of 13 except in those limited circumstances where we believe that such collection is permitted under COPPA. 

If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to ue, he or she can contact us via e-mail. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived in web logs and back-up archives after we delete the information from its active database (see above regarding web logs, and below regarding archived information). 

We believe that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from otherwise disclosing online their name, address and other personal information without parental permission. 

**Other**

We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems and maintenance of registration information in a separate database. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. 

We may offer chat, user reviews, multi-player games, bulletin board, or other public functions and any posting by you is considered public information available to other users. Any posting is governed by our Terms of Use. You should take care to not use personal information in your screen name or other information that might be publicly available to other users. 

If a user elects to use our site for informing a friend about our site or particular features or content, we ask them for the friend's name and e-mail address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit our site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. 

Your personal information is password-protected, and you should take appropriate measures to protect the secrecy of your password. If you use a computer in a public place or share a computer with others, remember to sign out and close your browser window when you finish a session with us in order to prevent others from accessing your personal information. 

We maintain archives of our web logs, database, and other systems and information. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived after we delete the information from its active database (see above regarding web logs). We maintain archives for disaster recovery, legal and other non-marketing purposes. 

Learn more about [How Google uses data.](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/)

**Binding Agreement**

Your use of our site, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. By using our Site, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the statement has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes. 06/01/2013
